A Guide to the Records of Community Learning Week 1979-1998
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
The Records of Community Learning Week 1979-1998
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
AR-0006
This collection is 24 linear feet in size.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content Information
These records reflect the activities and events of Community Learning Week (CLW) at Virginia Union University and in the Richmond community. CLW was organized in 1979 by the Richmond Committee of Black Clergy and the Office of Student Development at Virginia Union University. Rev. T.C. Milner headed the clergy group and Dr. Grace Pleasants directed the Virginia Union University office. The intent was to bring together the community to honor the memory and mission of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Pleasants served as program coordinator with Milner assisting until 1983 when Milner became program director. The week-long celebration includes a Community Leaders Breakfast and educational and cultural events throughout the city.
Contents List
- 1979-1998
  - 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1980 (Box 1)
  - 1981 (Box 1)
  - 1982 (Box 1)
  - 1983 (Box 1)
  - 1984 (Box 1)
  - 1985, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1986, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1987 (Box 1)
  - 1988, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - 1989, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1990, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1991, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - 1992, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - 1993, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - 1994, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - 1995, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1996, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - 1997, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1998, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Action Reports- Collections
  - Action Reports (Box 2)
  - Administration (Box 2)
  - Administration- General (Box 2)
  - Administration- General Information Folder (Box 2)
  - Administration-1984 Wrap-Up Meeting 1-2; 2-2 (Box 2)
  - ADS (Box 2)
  - Advertising (Box 2)
  - Agenda, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Agency Dinner, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Agency Forum Dinner, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Agency Forum Report (Box 2)
  - Announcements (Box 2)
  - Area Colleges and Universities (Box 2)
  - Articles, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Audience Development Plan (Box 2)
  - Awards (Box 2)
  - Beloved Community Bulletin (Box 2)
  - Bills/Invoices, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Biographs- One Day Conference Participants (Box 2)
  - Bio/Photographs, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Breakfast First Program (Box 2)
  - Breakfast Program (Box 2)
  - Budget 1-2; 2-2, 9 folders (Box 2)
  - Budget/Expenses (Box 2)
  - Budget Proposal (Box 2)
  - Business Connection (Box 2)
  - Calendar of Events, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Campus Activities, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Center for Black Enterprise (Box 2)
  - Certificates, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Cheryl (Box 2)
  - Church Directory- Clergy (Box 2)
  - Church Support (Box 2)
  - City of Richmond (Box 2)
  - Civil Rights and Race (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Clipping Collection 1979-1987, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Collections, 6 folders (Box 2)
- Colleges and Universities Relation Activities- Faculty and Staff Directory
  - Colleges and Universities Relation Activities (Box 3)
  - Committee-Youth, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Communication (Box 3)
  - Community Collaborative for Youth (Box 3)
  - Community Leaders Breakfast, 5 folders (Box 3)
  - Community Program 20th Anniversary (Box 3)
  - Community Workshop Service (Box 3)
  - Conference (Box 3)
  - Conference Evaluation Report (Box 3)
  - Conference Planning (Box 3)
  - Conference Statement (Box 3)
  - Confirmation (Box 3)
  - Contracts (Box 3)
  - Co-Founder (Box 3)
  - COR 08-02 PA 282 (Box 3)
  - Corporate (Box 3)
  - Corporate Sponsors, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Corporate Support (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 8 folders (Box 3)
  - Correspondence/General (Box 3)
  - Correspondence/IN, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Correspondence/Out, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Council Minutes (Box 3)
  - Cover Letters (Box 3)
  - Cover Sheet (Box 3)
  - Creative Services, 6 folders (Box 3)
  - Creative Services Invitations (Box 3)
  - Current (Box 3)
  - Delivery Receipt (Box 3)
  - Department of Education (Box 3)
  - Director's Folder (Box 3)
  - Director's Luncheon, 5 folders (Box 3)
  - Director's Messages, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Director's Notebook (Box 3)
  - Director's Notes, 4 folders (Box 3)
  - Director's Papers, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Director's Project (Box 3)
  - Director's Reports, 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Director's Statement, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Director's Work Papers (Box 3)
  - Director's Worknotes (Box 3)
  - Director's Working Activity (Box 3)
  - Director's Working Drafts (Box 3)
  - Directory, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Directory Sponsors (Box 3)
  - Documents (Box 3)
  - Document Evaluation Plan (Box 3)
  - Document of Coretta's Visit (Box 3)
  - Document Sponsors, 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Document Present (Box 3)
  - Document Present Activity (Box 3)
  - Downtown Worship Service (Box 3)
  - Edcaps (Box 3)
  - Editorials (Box 3)
  - Education and the Courts (Box 3)
  - Education Project (Box 3)
  - Evaluation, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Event Honoring (Box 3)
  - Extra Copies (Box 3)
  - Faculties Request (Box 3)
  - Faculty and Staff Directory (Box 3)
- Fax-Incoming-Grant Worksheets
  - Fax-Incoming, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Fax-Outgoing, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Faxed Information, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Feature Program (Box 4)
  - Fee Report (Box 4)
  - Finances 1985, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Financial (Box 4)
  - Financial Reports 1-2; 2-2, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - Financial Sponsors (Free Report) (Box 4)
  - Financial Support Profile (Box 4)
  - Fiscal Affairs, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Fiscal Affairs 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Fiscal Affairs- Bill (Box 4)
  - Fiscal Affairs- Financial State (Box 4)
  - Follow-up, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Forms (Box 4)
  - Forms/Flyers (Box 4)
  - Forum Dinner (Box 4)
  - Full Program (Box 4)
  - Fundraising, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Fundraising Business, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Fundraising Clergy (Box 4)
  - Fundraising Corporate (Box 4)
  - Fundraising Cultural Event (Box 4)
  - Gala, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Gala 1988 Jan 16 (Box 4)
  - Gala Breakfast (Box 4)
  - Gala Program (Box 4)
  - Gala Salute (Box 4)
  - Gala Tickets (Box 4)
  - Gala Ticket Orders (Box 4)
  - Gala Ticket Programs (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Good News Herald (Box 4)
  - Governor's Breakfast Speech (Box 4)
  - Grace Pleasant's Forum Dinner (Box 4)
  - Grants (Box 4)
  - Grants Administration (Box 4)
  - Grants Worksheet (Box 4)
- Guide- Mass Meeting
  - Guide 1-2; 2-2 (Box 5)
  - Henrico County Martin Luther King, Jr. Celebration (Box 5)
  - Henrico Program (Box 5)
  - History, 5 folders (Box 5)
  - History Sponsor's Guide (Box 5)
  - I Have a Dream Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box 5)
  - Institutional Profile (Box 5)
  - Interfaith Service, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Invitations, 8 folders (Box 5)
  - Invitation Letters (Box 5)
  - Invoices (Box 5)
  - Issue Institute (Box 5)
  - Issue Roundtable (Box 5)
  - Journal, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - John F. Kennedy High Can Do Program 1989 Jan 30 (Box 5)
  - Kick-Off Ceremony 1998 Jan 13, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Kick-Off Program (Box 5)
  - Kick-Off Program 15th Anniversary (Box 5)
  - King (Box 5)
  - Leader Database (Box 5)
  - Leadership Institute (Box 5)
  - Learn-Action Resource Guide (Box 5)
  - Ledger Memorandums (Box 5)
  - Legislative Reception, 8 folders (Box 5)
  - Letter Collection In/Out (Box 5)
  - Letters Sent (Box 5)
  - Mailing Director (Box 5)
  - Mailing Lists, 6 folders (Box 5)
  - Mailing List Churches (Box 5)
  - Mailing List Corporate Sponsors (Box 5)
  - Mailing List Master (Box 5)
  - Major Program (Box 5)
  - Major Program Collection (Box 5)
  - Major Program Events (Box 5)
  - Management Directions (Box 5)
  - Management Events (Box 5)
  - Management Tools (Box 5)
  - Marketing 1-2; 2-2, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Marketing Promotion (Box 5)
  - Marketing Public Relations (Box 5)
  - Mass Meeting, 8 folders (Box 5)
- Mass Meeting Platform- Phographs Document
  - Mass Meeting Platform (Box 6)
  - Master Directory, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Master Mailing (Box 6)
  - Master Mailing List 1996 (Box 6)
  - Master Program Collection, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Master Schedule Guide (Box 6)
  - Mayor Event (Box 6)
  - MBG Collections (Box 6)
  - Memo (Box 6)
  - Memorial and Honors (Box 6)
  - Memory of King (Box 6)
  - Merit Collection Copy (Box 6)
  - Miller (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs Administration Organizations Profile (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs Biographies Main Speakers (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs Conferences/ Workshops/ Education (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs Director's Worknote (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs File Directory (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs Foundation (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs Media-Community Bulletin (Box 6)
  - Minority Affairs Program Journal 1985 (Box 6)
  - Minority Group Ads (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Mission (Box 6)
  - Mission and Goals (Box 6)
  - Mission Goals Concert Model (Box 6)
  - Minutes, 4 folders (Box 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Dialogue, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Holiday (Box 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Holiday Bill (Box 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Reception Program (Box 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars (Box 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Program, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Social Activities (Box 6)
  - Model Plan (Box 6)
  - MRS and Meeting (Box 6)
  - National Business (Box 6)
  - National Editorial, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - National Holiday (Box 6)
  - National King Holiday, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - National Model (Box 6)
  - Nation's Bank (Box 6)
  - News Clippings (Box 6)
  - News Clippings and Others (Box 6)
  - News Letters (Box 6)
  - News Letter Paper (Box 6)
  - Newspaper Feature Section (Box 6)
  - Non-Violent Social Change (Box 6)
  - Office Management Volunteers (Box 6)
  - OIG (Box 6)
  - One-Day Conference, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - One-Day Leadership Conference (Box 6)
  - One-Day Leadership Conference 1988 Jan 15 (Box 6)
  - One-Day Leadership Conference Participants (Box 6)
  - Originals (Box 6)
  - Other Community Events (Box 6)
  - Pepsi Seminar (Box 6)
  - Personnel Files (Box 6)
  - Phone Directory (Box 6)
  - Photograph Collection (Box 6)
  - Photographs Document (Box 6)
- Photograph Project Director- Programs and Layout
  - Photograph Project Director (Box 7)
  - Pilot (Box 7)
  - Planning 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Planning Resources (Box 7)
  - Plans of Operation 1-2; 2-2 (Box 7)
  - Pledge of Intent (Box 7)
  - Policies (Box 7)
  - Pre-Registration (Box 7)
  - Pre-Registration Forms, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Presentation Folder (Box 7)
  - Press Kit (Box 7)
  - Press Release (Box 7)
  - Printing (Box 7)
  - Profiles (Box 7)
  - Program, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Program 1980, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Program 1989-1996, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Program 1996 Collection (Box 6)
  - Program/Art Council (Box 7)
  - Program/Campus Service, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Program Collection 1-2; 2-2, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Program/Community Leaders Breakfast, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Program/Downtown Unity Services, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Program Events (Box 7)
  - Program Folder (Box 7)
  - Program Guide (Box 7)
  - Program Highlights (Box 7)
  - Program/Interfaith Service (Box 7)
  - Programmed (Box 7)
  - Program and Layout (Box 7)
- Program/Legislative Reception- Rules and Responsibilities
  - Program/Legislative Reception (Box 8)
  - Program Management (Box 8)
  - Program/Mass Meeting (Box 8)
  - Program/Marting Luther King, Jr. Community Worship Service, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Program/One-Day Conference, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Program/Organization Chart (Box 8)
  - Program Planning Guide (Box 8)
  - Program/Pleasant Forum Dinner (Box 8)
  - Program Policies (Box 8)
  - Program/Richmond Peace Education Center (Box 8)
  - Program/Seniors Program (Box 8)
  - Program Souvenir (Box 8)
  - Program/Virginia Union University Chapel Service (Box 8)
  - Program Worship (Box 8)
  - Program/ Worship Service (Box 8)
  - Program/Youth Day (Box 8)
  - Project Abstract, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Project Director, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Project Survey (Box 8)
  - Proposal Writing Guide and Checklist (Box 8)
  - Prospective SAC Members Additional Copies (Box 8)
  - Public Relations (Box 8)
  - Public Relations Council, 10 folders (Box 8)
  - Rainbow Coalition (Box 8)
  - Read-In, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Read-In Guide (Box 8)
  - Read-In Project (Box 8)
  - Read-In Registration (Box 8)
  - Reasons Bir Letter (Box 8)
  - Receipts, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Receptions (Box 8)
  - Reflections of the Spirit (Box 8)
  - Registration Forms 1996 (Box 8)
  - Registration Forms and Others (Box 8)
  - Registration and Lunch (Box 8)
  - Religion Resources (Box 2 folders)
  - Religion Resources 1985 (Box 8)
  - Religion Resources Guide, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Religious (Box 8)
  - Reports, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Report Forms (Box 8)
  - Resources King Center (Box 8)
  - Responses for October 1st (Box 8)
  - Revise Plan (Box 8)
  - Richmond Crusade for Voters (Box 8)
  - Richmond Free Press Features (Box 8)
  - Richmond Profile (Box 8)
  - Roles and Responsibilities (Box 8)
  - Rules and Responsibilities (Box 8)
- SAC Pledge Forms- Stationery
  - SAC Pledge Forms (Box 9)
  - Schedule (Box 9)
  - Schedule of Events, 6 folders (Box 9)
  - Schedule Worksheet (Box 9)
  - Scholar's Program (Box 9)
  - Scope of Work Plan (Box 9)
  - Senior Programs, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Service Affair (Box 9)
  - Service Committee (Box 9)
  - Souvenir Journal, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Souvenir Program (Box 9)
  - Special Section (Box 9)
  - Speech Collection, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Sponsors (Box 9)
  - Sponsors 1987 (Box 9)
  - Sponsors 1989 (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Advisory Council, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Checklist (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Confirmation Forms (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Council, 9 folders (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Council Directory (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Council Meeting 1987 Jun 30, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Directories (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Directory, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Event Confirmation (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Fees (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Folder (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Guide (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Invitation (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Mailing List (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Meeting (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Planning Meeting (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Pledge (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Profile (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Profile Minority Affairs 1986 (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Program, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Sponsor's Support Institution (Box 9)
  - Staff Minutes (Box 9)
  - Statewide Conference, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Stationery 1-2; 2-2 (Box 9)
- Steering Committee- Year-round Transition Plan
  - Steering Committee (Box 10)
  - Steering Committee Meetings 1989 June 29 (Box 10)
  - Steering Committee Members (Box 10)
  - Stock Accounts (Box 10)
  - S.T. Rhodes (Box 10)
  - Sub-Committee Notes (Box 10)
  - Summer Jobs 1986 (Box 1)
  - Talking Point (Box 10)
  - T.C. Millner (Box 10)
  - Telephone Messages (Box 10)
  - Ticket Problems (Box 10)
  - Tickets (Box 10)
  - Transition Concept Plan (Box 10)
  - Transition Plan, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Transmission Plan (Box 10)
  - Transmittal Sheet (Box 10)
  - University Chapel (Box 10)
  - University of Richmond Martin Luther King, Jr. Program (Box 10)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Virginia Council of Churches (Box 10)
  - Virginia Institute of Pastoral Care (Box 10)
  - Virginia Interfaith for Public Policy (Box 10)
  - Virginia Union University, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Virginia Union University Center Force (Box 10)
  - Virginia Union University Center Service (Box 10)
  - Virginia Union University Community Service Center (Box 10)
  - Virginia Union University Projects (Box 10)
  - Volunteers, 7 folders (Box 10)
  - Volunteers 1996-1997 (Box 10)
  - Volunteers Corp, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Volunteers Guide (Box 10)
  - Volunteers Project (Box 10)
  - Volunteers Registration (Box 10)
  - Volunteers Rules (Box 10)
  - Voucher 1-2; 2-2 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Union University Today Pullout Supplement (Box 10)
  - Wilder Connection (Box 10)
  - Will Focus (Box 10)
  - Women's Opportunity Network (Box 10)
  - Work Folder (Box 10)
  - Work for Ms. Himes (Box 10)
  - Worksheet Schedule, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Worship Service, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Wrap-up, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Year Plans (Box 10)
  - Year-Round, 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Year-Round Databases Form (Box 10)
  - Year-Round Opportunity Projects (Box 10)
  - Year-Round Program, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Year-Round Program Lot (Box 10)
  - Year-Round Program Seven Issue Areas (Box 10)
  - Year-Round Transition Plan (Box 10)
- Youth Day- YMCA Black Achieves
  - Youth Day, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Youth Day Directory (Box 11)
  - Youth Day Intent/Registration Forms (Box 11)
  - Youth Day Programs (Box 11)
  - Youth Day Responses (Box 11)
  - Youth Issues Forum (Box 11)
  - Youth Program (Box 11)
  - Youth Rally 1988 Jan 16 (Box 11)
  - YMCA Black Achieves (Box 11)
- Binders: Agency Dinner, Community Leaders Breakfast- Newspaper Clippings, Programs, Schedules and Statements
  - Agency Dinner, Community Leaders Breakfast, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Budget 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - Community Learning Week 1996 (Box 12)
  - Director's Notebook CLW Management 1990 (Box 12)
  - Document: 4th Annual Community Learning Week Planning Paper 1982 (Box 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Program, Schedules and Statements (Box 12)
- Binders: Nissan Press Information 1994- Volume II 1997
  - Nissan Press Information 1994 (Box 13)
  - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Proposal for Celebration (Box 13)
  - Southern Association for College and School 5th Year Report 1986 (Box 13)
  - Transportation Schedule (Box 13)
  - Tyler C. Millner and Associates Payroll (Box 13)
  - Volume I 1997 (Box 13)
  - Volume II 1997 (Box 13)
- Cassette Tapes
  - Mr. Chuck Stone S trategies of Empowerment: Risks and Rewards1983 Jan 12 (Box 14)
  - Mr. Chuck Stone What Price is Freedom Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. 1983 Jan 12 (Box 14)
  - Black Family Ritual 1983 Jan 13 (Box 14)
  - Dr. Vincent Harding: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. 1983 Jan 14 (Box 14)
  - Legislative Forum Unemployment 1983 Jan 15 (Box 14)
  - Martin Luther Kind Religious Service 1983 Jan 15
  - Book Review Dr. Noreece T. Jones, Jr. 1984 Jan 10 (Box 14)
  - Honor's Student Lecture 1984 Jan 10 (Box 14)
  - Issues Roundtable 1-2; 2-2 1984 Jan 10 (Box 14)
  - Social Science Lecture 1984 Jan 11 (Box 14)
  - Rev. Henry C. Garrard: Spiritual Renaissance 1984 Jan 12 (Box 14)
  - The King Malcolm X Debate 1984 Jan 12 (Box 14)
  - Virginia Union University 6th Annual Community Learning Week 1984 Jan 12 (Box 14)
  - Community Learning Week Breakfast 1984 Jan 13 (Box 14)
  - Guest Lecture Series: Attorney Elaine Jones 1984 Jan 13 (Box 14)
  - Martin Luther King: A World Without War: Rev. Curtis Harris (SCLS) and Christopher Krueglar (Harvard) 1984 Jan 14 (Box 14)
  - Virginia Union University Assembly: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Dreamer, Philosopher, and Leader. Henderson Center Dr. Preston Yancy, Miss Angela Powell, Mr. Byron Thomas, Carolyn Daughtry 1985 Jan 16 (Box 14)
  - Clergy Dialogue, Virginia Union University Dining Room. David Cohen, President of Social Development Corporation. Introduction Done by Bernard Kaplan. 1985 Jan 16 (Box 14)
  - Book Review Luncheon Form: Dr. Charles V. Willie. Topic: Race, Ethnicity and Socioeconomic Status 1985, Jan 17 (Box 14)
  - Community Leaders Breakfast: Dr. Herman Valentine 1985 Jan 18 (Box 14)
  - Community Learning Week Assembly, Virginia Union University 1985 Jan 18 (Box 14)
  - Henrico Martin Luther King Celebration at the Rising Mount Zion Church 1985 Jan 19 (Box 14)
  - Youth Event: Birthday Salute to Martin Luther King, Jr. 1985 Jan 19 (Box 14)
  - ND: Part II Martin (Box 14)
  - Mini-Cassettes: Community Learning Week, 2 folders (Box 14)
- Video Tapes
  - Community Breakfast at Virginia Union University 1983 Jan 10, tape #1 (Box 15)
  - Community Breakfast at Virginia Union University (Box 15)
  - Community Learning Week #1 (Box 15)
  - Community Learning Week #2 (Box 15)
  - Roundtable (Community Learning Week #3 and #4) 1984 Jan 10 (Box 15)
  - Community Learning Week Cut Aways #7, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Community Profiles (Box 15)
  - Georgia Power Summer Youth Program 1981 Sept 4 (Box 15)
  - Innervision: Mr. T.C. Millner (Box 15)
  - Inside Shots (Box 15)
  - Martin Luther King Higher Education Seminar 1983 Jan 13, Tapes #1 and #3 (Box 15)
  - Summer Youth Program New Horizons1982 (Box 15)
- Administrative and Miscellaneous
  - Administrative (Box 16)
  - Buttons (Box 16)
  - Commemorative Martin Luther King, Jr. Stamps (Box 16)
  - Education Conference Materials 1986 (Box 16)
  - Invitations (Box 16)
  - Newsletters (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Posters (Box 16)
  - Programs 1979-1982 (Box 16)
  - Programs 1983 (Box 16)
  - Programs 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Programs 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Programs 1988-1990 (Box 16)
  - Programs 1991-1993 (Box 16)
  - Programs 1994-1996 (Box 16)
  - Programs 1997-1998 (Box 16)
- Photographs
  - Photographs, head shots (Box 17)
  - Negatives (Box 17)
  - Photographs 1982 (Box 17)
  - Photographs 1986 (Box 17)
  - Photographs program 1988 (Box 17)
  - Photographs program 1992 (Box 17)
  - Photographs n.d. (Box 17)
  - Slides (Box 17)
- Miscellaneous Oversized
  - Magnet signs (Box 18)
  - Mounted color and b/w photographs with labels (Box 18)
  - Spiral notebook (Box 18)
  - Anheuser-Busch check replica for $5,000 (Box 18)
  - 2 framed 8 by 10 portraits of Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Union University Certificate of Sponsorship framed (Box 18)
  - Certificate of Recognition framed
  - Pencil sketch Martin Luther King, Jr. framed (Box 18)
  - Certificate of Recognition (Box 18)
  - Measure of a Man calendar poster n.d. (Box 18)
  - Measure of a Man calendar poster 1998 (Box 18)
  - Angel with Harp drawing by Shirlene Fuller (Box 18)
  - I Have a Dream speech laminated, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - CLW posters 1979, 1980, 1982, 1983, 1984, 1986, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Free at Last Poster, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Pencil sketch of Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box 18)
  - Old board from program- color sketch of Richmond skyline (Box 18)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Free at Last speech (Box 18)
  - Remembering Dr. King photograph (Box 18)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Federal Holiday Commission poster (Box 18)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. lecture/discussion at Virginia Union University A World without Warn.d. (Box 18)